(Sheldon:)let a barn spider
lay eggs in your nose.
(Sheldon:)The minute you sneeze web,
I'm moving out.
(Leonard:)I never thought
I'd say these words,
but come on, nose spider!
(Penny:)Who are you kidding?
(Penny:)You were so panicked
(Penny:)Leonard was gonna die,
you'll never leave him.
(Amy:)Sheldon will move out
eventually.
(Penny:)Yeah, once he figures out
how to work a door.
(Sheldon:)I was not panicked, and I am
not overly attached to Leonard.
(Leonard:)You were so worried
that you smashed your face
(Leonard:)trying to check on me.
You love me.
SHELDON:
Yeah. Tell me
(Sheldon:)those aren't the
words of a man
(Sheldon:)with a spider eating its
way through his brain.
(Sheldon:)Amy, you're a neuroscientist.
(Sheldon:)Crack his skull open,
spray some Raid in there.
(Bernadette:)I love that you take pride
in your looks,
(Bernadette:)even when I have
(Bernadette:)to pee in the morning,
(Bernadette:)and you're in there
spending an hour on your hair.
(Howard:)I love that you're too good
to pee in the kitchen sink.